<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks | UW Change Seminar</title>
    <link>https://change.washington.edu/event/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://change.washington.edu/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://change.washington.edu/media/logo_huba025b7a8743106165fbcade43568e72_15589_300x300_fit_lanczos_3.png</url>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/event/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Interest Computing: Pluralistic Design of Ethically Responsible AI and Policy</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/public-interest-computing-pluralistic-design-of-ethically-responsible-ai-and-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/public-interest-computing-pluralistic-design-of-ethically-responsible-ai-and-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Neil Gaikwad is a PhD candidate at MIT where he is also a Scholar of Social and Ethical Responsibilities of Computing and a fellow at the Dalai Lama Center for Ethics and Transformative Values. His research in Responsible AI and Policy brings a novel computational lens to high-stakes societal decision-making, specifically focusing on addressing issues of equity, ethics, and access within algorithmic systems. This research has been published in top conferences in artificial intelligence (AAAI) and human-computer interaction (CHI, CSCW, UIST). It has also been featured in The New York Times, New Scientist, Bloomberg, WIRED, and The Wall Street Journal. The impact of Neil&amp;rsquo;s research and teaching has received widespread recognition, including a Facebook PhD Fellowship, an MIT Human Rights &amp;amp; Technology Fellowship, a Rising Star in Data Science by the University of Chicago, a nomination for Schmidt Science Fellows, and an MIT GSC Graduate Teaching Award. For his contributions to advancing DEI values, he was honored with MIT&amp;rsquo;s highest student award, the Karl Taylor Compton Prize. Neil holds a master’s degree from the School of Computer Science at Carnegie Mellon University. For further information about his research and artistic pursuits, please visit: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.media.mit.edu/~gaikwad&#34;&gt;webpage &lt;/a&gt;, X &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/neilsgaikwad&#34;&gt;neilsgaikwad&lt;/a&gt;, arts on Instagram &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/p/BXLiMCshYo8&#34;&gt;neilgaikwad_creations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democratizing Making: Scaffolding Participation Using e-Waste to Engage Under-resourced Communities in Technology Design</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/democratizing-making-scaffolding-participation-using-e-waste-to-engage-under-resourced-communities-in-technology-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/democratizing-making-scaffolding-participation-using-e-waste-to-engage-under-resourced-communities-in-technology-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Dhaval is a Senior Lecturer at the University of Queensland, Australia. His research primarily focuses on Human-Centered Computing (HCC) and Computer-Supported Cooperative Work (CSCW). He runs a research group called the Compassion Lab, which focuses on designing technologies to support members from under-resourced communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Framework for Improving Web Affordability and Inclusiveness</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/a-framework-for-improving-web-affordability-and-inclusiveness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/a-framework-for-improving-web-affordability-and-inclusiveness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Rumaisa Habib is a first year PhD student at Stanford University. Prior to joining Stanford, they were an undergraduate at LUMS, Pakistan. Their research at LUMS primarily focused on improving the affordability of the Internet through both policy and technical solutions. They are broadly interested in designing improvements for the Web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapping Our Data for Good Journey: 10 Considerations for Teaching, Learning, and Practicing Data for Good</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/mapping-our-data-for-good-journey-10-considerations-for-teaching-learning-and-practicing-data-for-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/mapping-our-data-for-good-journey-10-considerations-for-teaching-learning-and-practicing-data-for-good/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Dharma Dailey (she/her) is a Research Associate at UW’s eScience Institute . She also teaches community-engaged design in the Computing &amp;amp; Software Systems Division at University of Washington Bothell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quipu: Leveraging AI to build an alternative credit score for informal businesses in Latin America</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/quipu-leveraging-ai-to-build-an-alternative-credit-score-for-informal-businesses-in-latin-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/quipu-leveraging-ai-to-build-an-alternative-credit-score-for-informal-businesses-in-latin-america/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Viviana Siless is a full-time professor and researcher of AI at the School of Business at the University Torcuato Di Tella. She obtained her master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science at the University of Buenos Aires Argentina, and her Ph.D. from the University Paris-Sud/INRIA, under the supervision of Bertrand Thirion and Pierre Fillard. She spent 6 years as a postdoctoral fellow at the Martinos Center, MGH, Harvard Medical School. Her research work in computational neuroimaging focused on improving the diagnosis of neurological diseases by using MRI. Her work focused on unsupervised hierarchical clustering, graph matching, multi-modal 3D surface generation, multi-modal registration, and deep learning for data harmonization. Before her PhD, she worked 4+ years as a full stack software developer. In 2018 she co-founded Quipu Bank, to improve liquidity in the informal economies of LatAm. Viviana is the CTO, and directs the technical team, and leads the AI credit score building and the blockchain development and definitions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mercedes Bidart is the co-founder and CEO of Quipu Bank, a platform that enables communities to re-design their economies by changing the way micro-businesses’ credit assessment is done. She is passionate about the potential of technology to foster civic and economic collaboration in marginalized communities. Her passion to build economic justice stems from her experience in her home country, Argentina, where she ran community development projects in informal settlements with the NGO TECHO and worked for CIPPEC’s Cities Program building capacity across local governments in Latin America. She moved to the US in 2017 to pursue a Masters in City Planning at MIT. While at MIT, beside building Quipu, she collaborated with the Community Innovators Lab, U.Lab, MIT CREATE, the SPURS Program and Presencing Institute’s ‘Societal Transformation Lab’, a global network of teams leading system change initiatives. After MIT, she moved to NYC to advise the Deputy Mayor for Policy Strategy of the City on ‘new economy’ strategies to support minorities and women owned businesses. Mercedes’ work was featured in Forbes, Norman Foster Stories, and El Pais; and was awarded by SOCAP, MIT Innovation Initiative, MIT DesignX Accelerator, World Bank Youth Summit, IDB Lab among others. Quipu was awarded by Fast Company as one the ten most innovative companies in LATAM in 2022 and Accion Center of Financial Inclusion as one the world’s 50 more inclusive fintechs. She holds a master degree from Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Fulbright Scholar) and a Bachelor in Political Science from the University of Buenos Aires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eKichabi v2: Designing and Scaling Digital Information Systems in Sub-Saharan Africa</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/ekichabi-v2-designing-and-scaling-digital-information-systems-in-sub-saharan-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/ekichabi-v2-designing-and-scaling-digital-information-systems-in-sub-saharan-africa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Alex Metzger is a UW Computer Science and Mathematics major with interests in violin, tennis, and machine learning. He&amp;rsquo;s currently interning at Gooey.AI doing AI work with Digital Green to help Agricultural Extension workers help farmers. He&amp;rsquo;s been part of the eKichabi project since last September - developing/maintaining the Django Server and Android integration, and co-first authoring the technical paper submitted to ACM CHI. He&amp;rsquo;s currently a technical consultant for the continuation of the project aimed at studying the economic impacts of the intervention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eHealth Data Security and Privacy of HIV Care in Malawi</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/ehealth-data-security-and-privacy-of-hiv-care-in-malawi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/ehealth-data-security-and-privacy-of-hiv-care-in-malawi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Lisa Orii is a PhD student in Computer Science &amp;amp; Engineering at the University of Washington. She is advised by Richard Anderson. Her research examines applications of technologies in healthcare settings in low- and middle-income countries. Lisa’s current focus is researching the potential of mobile health tools for improving healthcare workers’ decision-making in clinical settings with limited resources. She is a Funai Overseas Scholarship Recipient and a member of the inaugural cohort of the Quad Fellowship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Years of ICTD Research at UW CSE</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/20-years-of-ictd-research-at-uw-cse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/20-years-of-ictd-research-at-uw-cse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talk Recorded&lt;/strong&gt;: Yes (&lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1RADxdq3nhIa784yGXw_4aRSjEz6WqikB/view?usp=drive_link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Link to recording&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/95254816636&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Richard Anderson is a Professor of Computer Science and Engineering, where he has been on the faculty since 1986, with brief leaves to Indian Institute of Science, Microsoft Research, and PATH. His research has focused on computing for the developing world since 2005, when he became involved with the Digital Study Hall project. In 2009, Richard spent a sabbatical year working with the Digital Health Solutions group at PATH, a global health NGO based in Seattle. This opportunity allowed him to increase his efforts on applying computing technologies to challenges in global health. While working with PATH, he co-founded the Projecting Health project, which used the Community-Led Video Education model to promote healthy practices in rural areas in India.  His research interests in ICTD include technologies for behavior change communication, improving tools to support the use of data in strengthening health systems, and digital financial services.  In 2020 he received the ACM Eugene L. Lawler Award for Humanitarian Contributions within Computer Science and Informatics for contributions bridging the fields of computer science, education, and global health.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An African Perspective to Regulating Self-Driving Cars</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/an-african-perspective-to-regulating-self-driving-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/an-african-perspective-to-regulating-self-driving-cars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WHO-UNICEF Technical Expert Advisory Group on Nutrition Monitoring (TEAM) on designing effective data visualizations (authored by the Tricia)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Jake Okechukwu Effoduh is a Vanier Scholar at the Osgoode Hall Law School, conducting doctorate research on the Legitimization of Artificial Intelligence in Africa. He is also a Queen Elizabeth Advanced Scholar with the Open Africa Innovation Research (OpenAIR), and a Partner at Praxis &amp;amp; Gnosis Law in Nigeria. He founded Law2Go in 2018, a digital library of human rights laws and legal services for Nigeria and he has been a human rights lawyer since 2011. With a demonstrated history of advocacy across domestic and international systems, Effoduh has worked within the justice sector in Nigeria, the West African ECOWAS human rights system, the African Human Rights Commission, and the UN Human Rights Council.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;www.google.com&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computational prosthetics for a wounded body politic: designing for generative justice </title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/computational-prosthetics-for-a-wounded-body-politic-designing-for-generative-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/computational-prosthetics-for-a-wounded-body-politic-designing-for-generative-justice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Dr. Ron Eglash is a Professor in the School of Information at University of Michigan. He received his B.S. in Cybernetics, his M.S. in Systems Engineering, and his PhD in History of Consciousness, all from the University of California. His work as Fulbright scholar was published as African Fractals: modern computing and indigenous design. Other work, funded by NSF, HUD, and Department of Education, include the Culturally Situated Design Tools software suite; new practices in African architecture, and development for urban sustainability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;www.google.com&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Fact-Checking: Exploring The Reach of Current and Future Efforts to Counter Misinformation in the Global South</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/beyond-fact-checking-exploring-the-reach-of-current-and-future-efforts-to-counter-misinformation-in-the-global-south/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/beyond-fact-checking-exploring-the-reach-of-current-and-future-efforts-to-counter-misinformation-in-the-global-south/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;www.google.com&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight Kampala: Illuminating Energy Access Inequities in Informal Urban Communities</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/spotlight-kampala-illuminating-energy-access-inequities-in-informal-urban-communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/spotlight-kampala-illuminating-energy-access-inequities-in-informal-urban-communities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
June Lukuyu is an Assistant Professor in the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering at the University of Washington. She recently received her Ph.D. in ECE at the University of Massachusetts Amherst and an M.Sc. in Renewable Energy Systems Technologies from Loughborough University. Her research focuses on how to develop and plan for inclusive and sustainable energy systems and technologies for underserved communities, centering on promoting social development, sustainability, and human empowerment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;www.google.com&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Smart Home Technologies to Support Domestic Activities in the Global South</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/using-smart-home-technologies-to-support-domestic-activities-in-the-global-south/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/using-smart-home-technologies-to-support-domestic-activities-in-the-global-south/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WHO-UNICEF Technical Expert Advisory Group on Nutrition Monitoring (TEAM) on designing effective data visualizations (authored by the Tricia)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
George Hope Chidziwisano is a Presidential Postdoctoral Fellow in the Human Computer Interaction Institute at Carnegie Mellon University. His research focuses on designing sensing technologies for resource constrained areas. More specifically, he conducts design-oriented studies in the Global South, where he collaborates with local technicians and families to design, develop, and deploy novel sensing technologies that have the potential to solve some of the challenges facing homes. Hope’s research has received recognition from Google Research and ACM COMPASS. Hope was a fellow in the Data Science for Social Good program; a program affiliated with the University of Washington’s eScience Institute. He used his expertise in machine learning, natural language processing and deep learning to contribute to a project on identifying disinformation in online news articles. Hope has also participated in the Global Innovation Exchange program (University of Washington and Tsinghua University) where he practiced a variety of human-centered design methods to develop novel sensing techniques, user-friendly interfaces, and cutting-edge computer technologies. Before joining CMU, Hope completed his Ph.D. and M.A. in Information and Media at Michigan State University. Hope completed his undergraduate studies in Computer Science and Physics at the University of Malawi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;www.google.com&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reimagining Human-Centered Design: Considering Reflexivity, Speculation and Long-term Engagement in ICTD</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/reimagining-human-centered-design-considering-reflexivity-speculation-and-long-term-engagement-in-ictd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/reimagining-human-centered-design-considering-reflexivity-speculation-and-long-term-engagement-in-ictd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.susanwyche.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt; https://www.susanwyche.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Susan Wyche is an Associate Professor in the Department of Media and Information at Michigan State University and has a courtesy appointment in MSU&amp;rsquo;s African Studies Center. Her research focuses on human computer interaction (HCI) and information and communication technologies and development (ICTD). Her work has been supported by Google, Facebook, the United States Agency for International Development (USAID), the National Institutes of Health (NIH), and the National Science Foundation (NSF). Wyche is a 2015 recipient of an NSF CAREER Award. Wyche received her Ph.D. in Human-Centered Computing from Georgia Tech, an MS from Cornell University and an undergraduate degree in Industrial Design from Carnegie Mellon University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;www.google.com&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boring Utilities Don&#39;t Exist: Community networks and the long term maintenance of equitable infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/boring-utilities-dont-exist-community-networks-and-the-long-term-maintenance-of-equitable-infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/boring-utilities-dont-exist-community-networks-and-the-long-term-maintenance-of-equitable-infrastructure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Rob Johnson, 31 started his professional life as an electrical engineer for New York&amp;rsquo;s MTA and has gradually found his way into the world of public policy and broadband. He currently works for the NY State Broadband office and volunteers with NYC Mesh. He also enjoys local politics, riding trains, singing, running, and climbing on rooftops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;www.google.com&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing global health data for epistemic justice</title>
      <link>https://change.washington.edu/talk/visualizing-global-health-data-for-epistemic-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://change.washington.edu/talk/visualizing-global-health-data-for-epistemic-justice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--(

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
)
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for Attendees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WHO-UNICEF Technical Expert Advisory Group on Nutrition Monitoring (TEAM) on designing effective data visualizations (authored by the Tricia)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seminar Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://washington.zoom.us/j/93100061611&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Tricia is a PhD student in the Department of Human Centered Design and Engineering (HCDE) at University of Washington. Prior to joining HCDE, Tricia worked in global health for over ten years after receiving her Master of Science in Public Health in International Health/Health Systems from Johns Hopkins School of Public Health (JHSPH). She is interested in applications of human centered design in global health including ethical data visualization and storytelling for decision-making in low- and middle-income countries (LMICs). She has pioneered research in global health data data visualization preferences and sensemaking among LMIC decision-makers and usability studies. She has trained over 1000 individuals on visualizing global health data based on contextual needs. She has faculty affiliation with JHSPH and is a consultant for Gates Ventures&amp;rsquo; Exemplars in Global Health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;www.google.com&#34;&gt;Talk Recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
